由于获取天气的任务是在fragment里面运行的  所以
Since the fetch weather task is in the fragment, the
启动这个任务的菜单项也应该在fragment里面
menu option to trigger that task should be inside the fragment
也就是说  我们需要为这个Fragment创建一个新的菜单布局文件
too. That means we should create a new menu layout
我们把它命名为forecastfragment.xml  这个文件会
for the fragment and we'll call it forecastfragment.xml. The file will
存放在资源目录下面的menu文件夹里面
live within the menu folder under the Resources directory. Inside
在这个文件的里面  我们声明了新的刷新菜单  并赋予
that file, we'll declare the new menu option for refresh and
它一个菜单项id  我们同时需要定义一个
give it this menu item id. We'll also need to define
Refresh这个词的字符串资源  我们现在来一步步的操作
a string label for this word, Refresh. We're taking this one
先把这个练习中学会修改菜单的
step at a time, so just make the menu xml
XML文件  如果你编译并运行这个应用
file change in this exercise. If you compile and run
看起来界面没有什么变化  菜单还没有
the app, there'll be no visible change. It won't show
显示在设备上  因为我们还没有从xml文件创建菜单按钮
up on the device yet because we haven't inflated the menu
创建按钮部分将在这之后的代码测试部分实现
item. Inflating it will be in the coding test after
请将菜单main.xml的实现作为参考
this. See how the menu main.xml is implemented as an
另外提醒一下  看一下下面的菜单训练指南
example. For an additional hint, see the menu training guide
当你完成的时候  你可以在这里勾选上这个按钮
below. When you're done, you can click on this box here.